Hold it right there, Polly!
You're not getting away this time!
I'm telling you, I'll get you the money!
You just have to wait a little longer!
Is that...
Yes, it's Polly.
The debt collectors are after him again.
Give us the money!
For the last time, I can't give
you money if I don't have it!
Stop making excuses and pay up!
You're gonna chase me all the
way to my grave, aren't you?
Yaggaras, and just in time, too.
Rope, action!
Hey, that's one of the shipwrights
from Galley-La, ain't it?
Sorry, fellas, but I gotta
borrow those yaggaras now!
Time for my round turn!
Awwww!
You punk! Just wait!
We'll get you next time!
So long, gentlemen!
It was a wonderful race, as always!
Take care, and maybe you
can try again next week!
Goddammit!
I gotta admit, for Jagera, you sure
have a good sense of dramatic timing.
That was close.
Those shipwrights of yours have
got some pretty fancy moves.
That they do.
Hey, buddy, thanks for the help!
I was starting to think we'd
never see our money again!
Money?
Oh, it must mean this.
Hello! No!
You gotta be kidding me.
Hey, come back here!
I'll take care of this.
Jerk's stealing our stuff.
I'll get your money back.
Huh?
Wait, a pigeon?
Okay, let me go, let me go.
Take it easy.
Jeez.
I'm not gonna run away.
You got me.
You win, all right?
You can stop pitching my ear now. Ah!
I was lucky enough to find
that money and you screw it up.
Better watch your back, Lucci.
I'll remember this.
Don't pay back your debt with
someone else's money, idiot!
Have you no shame?
Hey, I happened upon that
money fair and square!
Stealing from thieves is still stealing!
I didn't steal anything.
I was just borrowing
the Yagata, that's all.
Looks like they're back.
That's great.
I'm glad things worked out for you, Usopp.
Worked out for me?
That 200 million was for
ship repairs, remember?
That's right!
And all you did was sit there and stare
like a fool while I nearly got carried away!
I know, but the physician
said he'd handle it.
Well, that was embarrassing.
Rest assured, we will deal with
our employee appropriately.
Allow us to handle this so
there's no bad blood between you.
Although Polly's behavior
was reprehensible,
it's fortunate that he saved your
money from the Franky family.
Well, I guess you could
look at it that way.
No harm done, right?
So, who is this Franky family?
Do they rob from everyone
they run into or just us?
Well, it depends, but
normally they dismantle ships.
You mean they're workmen?
I don't know about you, but I'd never
hire a team that looks like that.
Indeed.
But they're not just ship dismantlers.
They're also bounty hunters.
Every time they find out there are pirates
in town, they cause quite a ruckus.
To put it simply, they're
just a public nuisance.
Not only do they collect bounties
on the pirates they defeat,
they also take possession of their ships.
Afterwards, they dismantle them and sell
whatever parts they can on the open market.
It may seem underhanded, but
for them, it's good business.
What a bunch of jerkwads!
It's like they're trying to
dismantle the whole pirate lifestyle!
Well, if they catch you, they
will certainly bleed you dry.
I don't know.
Those guys look too weak
to do anything to us.
The men you saw were underlings.
Franky, the leader of the group,
is not nearly as harmless.
If I were you, I would
avoid him at any cost.
Here you go iceberg, do
with him as you will.
I'm here, you can let go.
Excellent work as always, Lucci!
Truly, I can't apologize enough
for the actions of this elf.
It is talking.
Tell the nice people
that you're sorry, elf.
That pigeon really has it out
for that dude, doesn't he?
So the little bird talks but
the guy in the hat doesn't?
Anyway, I'm just glad we got our money
back Oh, so these belong to you, huh?
Good thing I was around.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
If you want to thank me, give me 10%.
Again, I'm quite sorry.
This imbecile is addicted
to gambling, you see.
He's racked up such a
massive debt that it's
made him lose sight of
everything but greed.
I don't care about him.
I want to know why you're talking.
I've had about enough of you
running your mouth, Lucci.
This'll shut you up. Rope. Action!
Kukalukaku!
Blueno!
Punishment!
Oh no, he's serious, isn't he?
Hook, line and sinker!
Is he okay?
Well, this is nothing new.
Whoa, check it out!
I thought he landed on his head,
but he stopped himself with his arm.
Wow!
Not only that, but he dug
his hand into the ground.
What, does he have fingers
of steel or something?
These guys are just shipwrights.
What do they need all
these crazy powers for?
Hey, you with the goggles on your head!
Listen, man, think
about this for a second.
That guy wasn't the one
saying all that mean stuff.
It was the pigeon!
The bird could say whatever it was.
Actions speak louder than words,
and Lucy's the one who hit me.
Yeah,
but the pigeon made him hit you because
he's too much of a coward to do it himself.
Hey, pigeon!
Get down here and fight your own fights!
Oh you want some more I'll take
you on any time enough Paulie?
Please excuse us for all the fuss.
I'm Rob Luke I mean my name's
Huttery and this is Rob
Lucci we both welcome you to
at the Gallylaw's factory.
Coo-coo-doo-coo!
Hold on, the pigeon almost introduced
himself as that guy, didn't he?
Oh, cool!
This is the ventriloquism
act, isn't it? Really?
You were the coolest
trash-talking pigeon ever!
Even I couldn't tell it was you,
and I'm usually pretty sharp!
No, please, it's really
nothing special at all.
Kaku!
He's just a weirdo who doesn't know
how to talk to people on his own.
Hold on a second, what does
that woman think she's doing?
Huh?
What do you mean?
Have you no shame?
Huh?
Don't play dumb with me, you harlot!
I can see way too much leg!
Cover up and show a
little decency, will ya?
This duck is a man's workplace, you know?
Now, now, Polly.
Let's calm down.
You too, Khalifa!
How many times have I told you those
clothes of yours are not appropriate?
If you want to look professional,
you should wear pants or at
least ankle-length skirts!
This guy's got issues.
He's serious, isn't he?
Well, enough of that.
Let's open the gate and
start the tour already.
That's just about the
biggest door I've ever seen.
And, whoa, you have to
open that thing by hand?
Wait, those two can't open
that on their own, right?
Whoa, I guess they can.
Well,
each doc only has five foremen,
and despite their peculiarities,
these two are both talented enough
to hold a position at Doc 1.
Kaku, who you met earlier,
is a foreman, too.
In a place like this, talent
is the only thing that matters.
So even if they're a bit
strange, we don't mind.
They are pretty weird, though.
Ha, we can go in now.
Remember to keep a
close eye on your money.
Not that I'm saying we have
thieves inside, mind you.
Yeah, I'm really sorry you
got dragged into that mess.
I should have known better.
Luffy, wait!
Do a better job of protecting
me next time around!
Okay, no problem. I got this. I'm worried.
I got this.
Doc One employs the strongest
workers of the Galley-La Company.
We take on our most
difficult requests here.
Come on, let's take a look inside. Oh!
Whoa!
It's super huge!
I knew it was going to be awesome,
but it's even better up close!
No kidding! Yeah!
Ooh, look over there!
They're building a big galleon!
I wonder who it's for!
Wow, they've got a full
force working here.
Now, this way, if you will.
Whoa, you guys see that?
Iceberg's here. Hey!
Look sharp for the boss, everyone.
Good morning, Mr.
Iceberg.
Nice to see you here, sir.
Hey, boss, could you take a
look at the outer panels for me?
Sure, I'll stop by later.
Lovely day, you ate it, Mr.
Iceberg.
Well, that depends on
how the project's going.
We're actually ahead of schedule, sir.
I guess Ice Pops is pretty
popular around here, huh?
In a place where skill is everything,
it's only natural that he shines.
It's interesting.
Although shipbuilding has
always been a thriving business,
before Iceberg's time, it was divided
between seven competing companies.
Regardless,
when he showed up,
there was something about his talent
that united everyone in the city.
With so many workers flocking to him,
it wasn't long before he made
the seven companies into one.
And five years ago, Galley-La was born.
His passion for shipbuilding
has never diminished,
and neither has the respect
that the craftsmen show for him.
The people here take pride in their
work so they don't bow down to anyone.
That goes for pirates and
marine officers alike.
That's the spirit this shipyard embodies.
Hey, buddy, I hear you're
a pretty good shipwright.
How would you feel about joining my crew?
Sound like fun?
What the hell are you
trying to pull here, kid?
You insolent little wretch!
Now, now, he was trying
to pay him a compliment.
He doesn't know any better.
Does this mean you sailed all the way to
Water 7 without any
shipwrights on your crew?
Yeah, that's one of the
reasons why we're here.
We need to have our ship repaired, but
we're looking for a new crew member, too.
We certainly have plenty of
shipwrights to go around,
but I wonder if any of them would
be willing to join a pirate ship.
Well, if you can find someone who agrees
to go with you, I won't get in the way.
You really mean it?
Wow, I see why people like you.
My offer still stands, you know.
Well, I probably shouldn't.
I am the mayor. So what?
By the way, Kalifa mentioned earlier that
Nico Robin was a member of your crew,
is that correct?
Sure is.
She's nice to have around
since she's so smart.
What's up?
There's not something
wrong with her, is there?
Oh, no.
I could watch them do this stuff all day.
Keep it steady. No need
to rush. We got this.
We gotta get a cannon like that to
put on the Mary, that'd be awesome.
Whoa, it's so shiny and long!
A real Timmy Culvering cannon.
Wow, they've really got everything.
I wonder what it feels
like to fire one of those.
Here's our chance.
Looks like it's made of copper.
And it's super expensive.
I wonder if they'd let me try it out?
Oh, wait a sec.
We've got 300 million
berries, I almost forgot.
We can afford at least
one of those, no problem.
Maybe two or three.
Hmm?
Did that guy with the nose leave already?
Huh? Kaku?
Where'd you run off to?
An assessment.
Wow, you are fast, huh?
I take it you checked the ship?
That I did, Missy.
Now, that's a coincidence.
We were wondering where you were.
They told me while they're
here, how was the ship?
About that.
Loopy!
Get down here!
What?
You better not be lying.
Because if this is a joke,
I'm sure as hell not laughing.
I wouldn't lie about something like this.
I'm a professional.
Something happen to Usopp?
Well, he was looking at the cannons
over there a second ago, but...
Hey! You there!
These bags are yours, aren't they?
Usopp was supposed to be taking care
of those, but yeah, they're ours.
Thanks, buddy.
I can't believe that idiot
wandering off at a time like this.
And how can I leave our
precious money alone like that?
Your money?
Yeah, those bags you found have
200 million berries in them.
You're funny, kid.
You wish. See ya.
Man, that's a good one.
So, how much do you think the
repairs are going to cost?
We've got plenty of money to spend,
and no price is too high for our Mary.
And while you're at it, why
don't you make her stronger,
faster, as tough as nails, and, of
course, decked out with cannons?
I'd like some pretty engravings or
some kind of decoration along the hull.
Also, can you guys renovate the inside?
Not so fast.
That ship of yours, she's gone on some
really extraordinary journeys, hasn't she?
Yeah, you bet, we've done it all.
A while back we flew in the
sky, then fell back down.
We climbed a big mountain, too.
So, you've got to work hard to
fix her up extra good, okay?
Her battle scars are far
worse than you think.
Um, then you're saying it's going to
take a long time for you to fix her?
No, ma 'am.
It's not about the time.
It's not about skill, either.
I'm saying no one can
fix her. Not even us.
So that means the keel's
damaged huh that's
right it looks like it's
taken a real wallop.
No way we we've gone
everywhere without any problems
until now in theory even if
we did everything we could
the probability of your ship
lasting till the next island?
is zero.
Mary, tell me.
Is what he said true?
You'll never sail again?
This sucks
I'm sorry Sanji I was so
focused on the books that I
didn't notice when she left
There's nothing you should have
to apologize for I just
assumed that the person I saw
walking with Robin had to have
been you and your human form
Which begs the question
who was that masked man
and how were they able
to disappear so suddenly
Yeah even Robin's scent disappeared
I hope everything's all
right I feel uneasy do
you need an examination
no that's not what I meant
It's what Aokiji said
his words keep repeating
what did he say that
worries you it was all that
Terrible stuff he said
about Robin's past and
then very soon we'd regret
her being on our crew
Oh yeah right so do you
think what he said might
have had something to do
with her disappearance?
I don't know.
But I know we're getting
nowhere looking for her.
Let's head back to the ship for now.
If nothing's wrong, she'll come
back on her own eventually.
Yeah, you're right.
What?
You can't fix the going, Mary? Why not?
I thought all of you were supposed
to be awesome shipwrights.
Don't worry about the money.
Look, we got plenty.
It's not about the money, son.
No matter how much you pay, that ship
can't be restored to how she used to be.
To be honest, I'm rather impressed you
were able to get that old girl this far,
considering the condition
that she's currently in.
What's that supposed to mean?
What exactly is going on with the Mary?
Do you know what the
keel is, immoral girl?
The thing at the bottom of the boat?
Yeah, it's the most important
piece of lumber on a ship.
It crosses from stem to
stern and provides support.
When you build a ship, you
start off by placing the keel.
Then you set the wood
for the stem, the stern,
the frame, frame brackets, and deck beams.
All of the pieces are
carefully assembled together,
with the keel serving as the core.
It's the very backbone framework
and life of every vessel
constructed and when it's severely
damaged Then that's the end of her.
You can't just replace it
with a new one That'd be
the same thing as building
a new ship from scratch.
That's the reason we or anyone
won't be able to fix her your ships?
Just a bunch of woods stuck
together awaiting her end.
Hey you don't say such horrible things
Horrible or not, it's the truth
Okay, fine, then.
Just rebuild her from the
ground up like you said before.
Build another Going Merry.
Cuckoo!
Sorry, not possible. Why not?
We could build you a very similar ship,
but no one can build you one
that would be exactly the same.
Nowhere in the world are there
two completely identical ships.
It simply can't be done.
What do you mean?
Why?
Tell me, are there any trees in the
world that grow exactly the same way?
A sailing ship is mostly
built out of lumber,
so the overall size and shape of a vessel?
is determined by the type of wood used.
That's why an exact
duplicate of your ship?
Can't be built by us or anyone.
even when using the same blueprints.
If we made a ship like that
with those specifications,
the ones who would
notice the difference and
feel that it's a
completely different ship?
would be all of you guys! Cuckoo!
No way.
So you're saying it's
absolutely impossible
for us to continue
sailing on the Going Mary?
Unfortunately, yes.
You can either wait
around for her to sink,
or you can dismantle her immediately.
A real Carabelle!
What a cool ship!
Have you guys seen the front?
It's totally awesome!
Okay, it's all done!
Now the Going Mary has everything
she could possibly need!
Well, your ship is on her last legs.
Why don't you look at
this as an opportunity?
You happen to be in the best place
in the world to buy a new ship.
You have money, right?
I understand that your ship was a caravel.
Sailing on the Grand Line in an old ship
like that would be difficult to begin with.
No way.
We're not getting a new ship. Luffy.
The Mary is...
The going Mary is the ship
of the Straw Hat Pirates.
If she's repaired, then
she can still sail.
She'll be fine.
You'll see.
She got us here today, didn't she?
And you tell us out of nowhere
she can't sail anymore?
I can't believe that. I won't.
You guys are saying that
because you don't know her.
You have no idea how strong she is.
Then your plan is to keep
sailing her until she sinks?
So, this is the decision
of the ship's captain?
This discussion is over for now.
Just think about it.
If you decide to buy a ship, let me know.
My people can help.
If you're able to spend $300 million, we
can build a state-of-the-art ship for you.
Khalifa?
Here, if you'd look this over, please.
It's a catalog of our
new and our used models.
Use it as a price reference.
Hey, Iceberg!
There's someone at the front
gate who wants to see you.
It looks like those world
government officials again.
Should I tell them you're unavailable?
Well, yes, please. Say I'm gone.
By the way, Lulu, you've
got quite a case of bedhead.
Oops, how embarrassing. My apologies.
Anyway, I'll ask them
to leave. Uh, thanks.
I appreciate it.
Hold it right there, Iceberg. Hmm?
Looks like you're here after all.
Hey, you two need to hide.
Government officials are here.
What? Uh, okay.
Well, hello again, Corgi.
As you can see, I'm not here today.
Yes, you are. Come now.
I've come all the way
out here by Sea Train.
Don't turn me away.
It's impolite.
For some reason, I detect
the scent of pirates.
Whatever.
In any case, I want to talk to you.
I don't like you. Go away.
Are you a child? Nuh-uh.
I'm totally an adult.
Hmm, then start acting like one.
There's something of special
importance I need to discuss with you.
I would appreciate it
if you'd hear me out.
Come, let's talk this over in private.
Those government guys
are so damn persistent.
What the hell do they
want with Iceberg anyway?
Look, it has nothing to do with us.
Probably political stuff.
Should I beat them up? I wouldn't.
I mean, they're government guys after all.
What?
What's wrong?
Something seemed weird about
these bags when I grabbed them.
They're really light.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Oh, come on, stop kidding around.
How could they be with
all of that money inside?
Hey, who's that?
What's with the screaming?
Idiots, what the hell are you...
Hey, lady, if you sit like
that, everyone can see your...
Don't tell me.
There's no way.
I don't want to look.
200 million!
Gone?
It's really gone!
Wait, look at these bags,
they're not even ours!
Hey, hey, keep it down! What's wrong?
Our money, our money's gone.
Finished, gone, disappeared.
What?
Polly, was it you again? Huh? No! Honest?
Why would I lie? You mean it?
They're so noisy.
Hey, Kaku, question for you.
Why were you hanging out with
the Franky family earlier?
What are you talking about?
I haven't been anywhere near a single
member of the Franky family all day.
That's strange. Huh.
I was so certain that I saw your
long nose. Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hold on a sec!
That's Usa!
You saw him with the Franky family?
Well, you could say he was with them,
or maybe you could say he
was being dragged away.
That's called kidnapping!
Luffy, we gotta find him!
Hey, hold on!
Where are you going to look?
Wait for me, Usopp!
Wait for me, Money!
I'm coming!
Hey, where can I find the
Franky family's hideout?
It's not really a hideout.
It's more like a workshop.
From where your ship is docked, it's
way up the seashore to the northeast.
It's off by itself.
You can't miss it.
It's called the Franky House.
What was he thinking?
There's no way he could find Usopp
in this place all by himself!
I
Can't keep looking for him right now!
Before I do anything else I need to
take this money back to the ship!
If I march in there demanding our 200
million back while holding 100 million!
I'd be asking them to
steal that money too?
Yagra, please take me to the bull shop.
Shortest route possible.
I'll take Zoro and the others
with me and teach them a lesson.
Stealing from pirates?
Franky family, that makes
you the lowest of the low!
First floor, Backstreet Shopping District.
Please proceed with caution.
Thank you, and have a wonderful day!
Hurry, I'm counting on you!
Oh, it's her problem.
Hey, watch where you're going!
I'm sorry, sir!
I hope Usopp was able to
escape from them, somehow.
This is terrible.
Where's this guy from?
Hey does anybody know him? Who is he?
What's with them?
Yeah gotta wait.
Hold on a second.
Stop. Stop.
Usopp!
Usopp! Usopp!
Hey, say something!
Are you alright?
Open your eyes! Usopp! Hey!
Usopp! Wake up!
Excuse me, but are you two
pirates by any chance? Shut up!
Stop scaring and mind your own business!
Oh no!
Usopp, who did this to you?
Was it the Franky family?
It was.
It happened because I'm weak.
They took...
They took all the money.
Nabi.
How can I face the others now?
We were finally able to fix the fairy.
I'm so ashamed.
Damn it!
Usopp, I understand.
Don't worry about the money.
We'll get it back together.
He's been beaten pretty badly.
I probably shouldn't move him.
Look, stay right here, okay?
I'm going to go back to the ship
to get the others to come and help.
Chopper will have you fixed
up good as new in no time.
And listen, don't worry about
the stolen money, all right?
From what I've heard, their hideout
isn't too far away from here.
We'll crush them and that'll
be the end of it, okay?
Hey, you think this is some kind of show?
Get lost!
Stay put, okay?
I'm going to get you some help.
I'll be right back!
Hurry, Yagoras! Go faster!
A runaway ball!
We were finally able to fix the berry!
No matter how much you pay, that ship
can't be restored to how she used to be.
Whether we decide to give
in and buy a new ship,
or we have someone else manage
to fix and improve the Mary.
If we don't put the entire
300 million into this,
our future journeys together
will be difficult for sure.
We need that money. All of it.
We have to get it back.
What? Is that true?
Well, that's what the shipwright said.
This ship It can't be fixed,
even if we have money!
Then, then what's going to
happen to the Mary? Beats me.
Honestly,
it really just depends
on how Luffy and the
others react after hearing the assessment?
Either way, I'm sure they'll get it
sorted out while they're at the shipyard!
It just seems so extreme.
I mean, look at her.
Same old Mary that she's always been.
We've traveled together on this ship all
the way from the East Blue to this place.
Why now?
You just answered your own question.
Human beings become stronger,
hardship after hardship.
But ships are different.
Their wounds just pile up.
It's so hard to accept.
And what is Usopp going to say
when he hears about all of this?
I don't want to leave her.
I love to marry.
I know, we all do, but
her wounds are too deep.
There's nothing we can do.
Mary's in trouble and
Robin's still missing.
I'm worried about both of them.
Hey, everyone!
Look, it's Nami and she's alone.
That's weird.
I wonder what happened to Luffy and Usopp.
Hi, Nami!
Is everything alright?
Ow, ow, ow!
200 million?
Yes, 200 million!
What do you think, bro?
Awesome, right?
Incredible.
You guys are amazing.
Now that we have this much money, we'll
be able to get what we've always wanted.
We actually did it, didn't we?
After three years, our
perseverance has finally paid off.
I'm stoked! Me too.
Every time we'd have a little money,
we'd bet it all on the Yagato races!
And lose every time!
Each time we'd collect a criminal's
bounty, we'd party and drink!
And spend it all!
We could never ever save up the 200
million berries that we needed, until now!
We finally have enough to get it done!
And then some!
You guys did a hell of a job!
Now then, I know it isn't much,
but here's five million berries
to show you how grateful I am.
Eat, drink, and have a blast!
That's our throne!
Party time!
What the hell?
What was that?
Show yourself!
What fool would dare to
oppose the Franky family?
Huh?
It's that weak thing we ran into earlier.
How did you even manage to stand up?
Give us our money back.
Give us our money back, you say?
Does that mean you're
one of the Straw Hats?
That's right, bro.
He totally is.
I was expecting all of the Straw
Hat crew to be really strong,
but this one's not at all.
Yeah, he's a complete
weakling. What a joke.
Mind your own damn business!
What's he doing?
You've got some guts trying to take
back the money all by yourself.
But I'm afraid I can't let you have it.
Give it back.
We need the money
to fix the berry.
Her scars are deep.
That's our money.
It's to heal her wounds, understand me?
You can't have it!
Give it back to me right now!
What are you so worked up about?
Seems like you love your ship quite a bit.
No matter whatever condition she's
in, this money belongs to us now.
Understand?
Damn you.
Unfortunately, in this world, stealing
from pirates isn't really seen as a crime.
Besides, this is probably dirty money
you swiped somewhere along the way here.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Just let us have it.
Maybe you could beg the Navy for help.
Nah, they'd just arrest ya.
Too bad for Straw Hat Luffy.
He's got himself a useless
crony who can't even
handle the simple task of
guarding a little money.
Such a shame. Ah!
Ah! Ah-ha-ha!
All right, boys.
Show them all the hospitalities of
the Franky House while I'm gone.
No time like the present to start
shopping with this pile of money.
Man, this is gonna be great.
Hold it! Sensual attack!
Exploding star!
remember my name long-nosed
boy it's Franky if you
want to leave this city alive
I'd suggest you never cross
me what are you guys doing
you call this
little kid soy
a weapon see you later long
nose thanks again for the 200
No! Wait! Give it back!
Give back the berry! You hear me?
Give it back!
No! Please!
I need to wait here
until Robin comes back.
If I march in with the others
right now, I'll just be in the way.
It'll be scary, too.
For now,
the best thing I can do is stay here,
guard the money, and protect the Mary.
Don't let me down, guys.
I'm counting on you.
Stop! Stop!
I remember correctly.
This is the place Nami was talking about.
Look, this is the Backstreet
Shopping District.
You go up this canal, turn, then here.
Usopp is right here. Got it.
Nami, where are those
dismantlers you mentioned?
The Franky family.
Show me.
Hey, Usopp!
I guess he left.
Are you sure?
Maybe you just screwed up the direction.
I'm not you, moron!
Shut your hole! Usopp!
What'd you say?
Look at this!
It's blood, see?
That idiot.
I guess he walked off
somewhere on his own.
Wait, you don't think that he...
Musop, no.
Huh?
Aaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
Help! Help! Luffy! Help!
Help!
What are you doing?
And where the hell did you fall from?
The shipyard!
I was trying to jump around like
that carpenter to look for Usopp.
Are you all right? Yeah.
Oh, that's right.
I almost forgot.
We've got a terrible problem.
Usopp was abducted, and so was the money.
We know.
That's why we're here.
Come on.
We were just about to head over to
the hideout of the guys that did it.
I'll bet that's where we'll
find Usopp and the money.
Maybe he felt responsible
about what happened and went
to settle the matter with
the Franky family on his own.
is he breathing chopper he's
unconscious but yes he's breathing
He'll live.
I can save him.
You wait out here for us.
Okay, Usopp.
We're gonna go level that
stupid house to the ground.